Living Hell is a action, horror, science fiction
film directed by Richard Jefferies.
In a top secret Cold War military project an unstoppable, malignant organism who feeds on
light and energy is unleashed threatening to destroy everything in its path.
Frank Sears, played by Johnathon Schaech.
Carrie Freeborn, played by Erica Leerhsen.
Colonel Eric Maitland, played by James McDaniel.
Glenn Freeborn, played by Jason Wiles.
Lt. Gregg Arbogast, played by Terence Jay.
Pfc. Kermit Shourt, played by Joshua Rollins.
Living Hell (aka Organizm - DVD title) is a 2008 horror television film written and
directed by Richard Jefferies, which stars Johnathon Schaech and Erica Leerhsen.
It premiered on Sci Fi Channel on February 23,  and
was released on DVD on June 10, 2008.
Budgeted at an estimated $4,500,000, the film was shot in only 29 days.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and intense.